Kosaku Kawajiri's shoes
are a little big on me.
To avert suspicion,
I have to gradually swap
them out with ones that fit me.
Hayato.
No goodbye?
Have a pleasant day.
Hurry, come quick!
Something horrible's downstairs!
It was so scary!
I thought I was going to die!
Scar yas that was,
now I get to melt into the arms of
the handsome man I love so much.
Oh Honey, oh Sweety, oh Baby!
It's so eerie…
a strange cat is in our basement!
A cat?
Breakdown, Breakdown
(Listen up)
(Listen)
Breakdown, Breakdown
(3, 2, 1) Let's Go!
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
Shining Justice begins to sprout
Brand-new bed town
Will we meet? Let's find out
Feeling the sea breeze from the cape
through the tunnel to the tower
We wander into the alley,
drawn to each other
A shadow melts into our hearts
But the golden spirits
shine a light to protect us
Let the voice of love
take you higher
Let the gathering forces
overcome time itself
1999 Bizarre Summer
Our courage keeps the town in bloom
Great Days
EPISODE 30
CATS LOVE YOSHIKAGE KIRA
It was really scary cause, cause…
Well, we were out of
mineral water and…
I thought I'd get some more
down in the basement.
Of course, I love cats.
I thought,
"What a sweet British Shorthair."
It had perfect proportions,
and those gorgeous yellow eyes
and velvety bluish-gray fur.
Now how did you get in here?
It's okay sweetie-pie…
Oh, don't be scared.
That must be how he got in.
But he can't stay
down here forever.
He might pee on that potato sack.
He probably has fleas.
Just avoid eye contact and
approach nice and slow, right?
That's it. I just need to show him
I'm not a threat.
See? I'm showing you my belly
and being submissive.
Let's be friends.
Why should I have to beg
for this cat's attention?
Scram, or you're gonna get it!
Got it? Don't test me!
Darn it!
You little!
He clung to the ceiling
like an insect!
But the scariest part was…
That cat… right around his throat…
he had a gapping hole.
A hole as big as a one-yen coin!
And then, from the opening,
I heard…
MREOW
A hole?
Could it be a wound
from the arrow?
I swung the broom at him like
a mad woman before he ran away.
Please, can you go down there
and look?
I'm really scared.
You said… he had a gash?
Hey… Is he gone? Did he run away?
No… He's dead.
Huh? What are you talking about?
W-Wait…
Glass from the bottles
cut his throat.
Wait a minute! I was just—
It was an accident.
It's no one's fault. Just bad luck.
You didn't do anything wrong.
No one did anything wrong.
Apparently,
he had a gash in his throat
before the accident, but…
Now there's no telling
he was a Stand user.
But I'm certain he wasn't…
Good morning, Morioh.
Nothing better than the morning
after heavy rain, right?
On my way to the studio,
I saw a beautiful rainbow
Wonder if it's still there?
"What is this place, mrrp?
Why am I here?
Meow, meow, "he thought.
"Two days ago,
someone got me with an arrow,
I thought I came out okay…"
"M-My body's totally different!
What happened to it…
It's all weird!
Why am I stuck here?"
he meowed in perplexity
Where in the world did he bury him?
I'm so sorry, sweetie.
May you rest in peace.
Then he wondered,
"Now who is this lady?
I've got a real bad feeling
about her."
"The broom! That's it!
Now I remember!
This woman…
That's right! All this glass got
stuck in me and I got paralyzed!
I'm in this whole mess…
because of that woman!"
he fumed
Once again,
confusion overcame him.
"What? Something just happened
When I let my anger for
that lady out, something happened"
My toenail? W-Why?!
Could it be a curse?
My god… from that cat?!
Having survived by his animal
instincts and inclinations,
he intuitively understood
his new power and how to use it.
This little bastard's…
a Stand user!
Why the hell is this thing growing
where I buried that cat?
What in god's name is it?
What did it do to that sparrow?
I didn't spot any Stand.
Most importantly,
should I consider it the enemy?
Does it want me dead or…
To be on the safe side,
I shall exterminate it.
Sleep after feeding.
Is it a type of plant
or is it an animal?
Eliminating it would be easy,
but a little investigation
certainly won't hurt.
The way it almost innately
looked back at me when I called it
seemed strangely cat like…
The way it almost had to
sniff my hand is uniquely feline.
It seems agreeable
to being petted as well.
The way it's letting out
that eerie purr
as it's about to fall asleep
is almost exactly like
the way a cat purrs.
But none of that tells me whether
it harbors any ill will toward me.
I'll find out for sure.
Hmm… It's angry,
but now I know it doesn't
want to do me any harm.
There's no doubt, it's the cat
I buried here yesterday
So it really did have a gouge
in its throat from the arrow!
Um, Honey?
It's her!
That spot scares me.
That's where I lost my nail…
The cat attacked out of anger
for the woman!
If she found out about this thing…
Gossip would eventually spread to
Jotaro Kujo and his bratty cohorts!
I can never let that happen!
That's where you
buried the cat, right?
It feels like a curse.
I'm really scared…
It's not buried here.
Now go back inside.
You're lying!
You're lying to protect me,
aren't you?
Shit! This cat means
trouble after all!
I may not know
what its Stand can do,
but I'll kill it nonetheless.
Deadly Queen!
I hate to do this, but you're
about to be permanently uprooted
Bomb type one, switch on!
What?!
I, I don't…! It can't be a dud!
So this thing did it?
It has anti detonation abilities?
Huh? Is that a plant?
Th-That plant is moving!
I told you to get back inside!
Huh?
Shinobu!
The moment Deadly Queen's bomb
was batted away, it exploded!
Could this thing's ability be…
The cat-until-yesterday plant
thought to itself,
"I will kill that woman!"
Your attacks on her end now.
I'm about to make you disappear.
"If this man wants to get in
the way, then I'll kill him too!"
The only possible explanation
for the lack of explosion
could be that it was
deprived of air.
The plant knew instinctively
the exact method of killing.
Could its Stand ability be
controlling the air?
It's coming!
I couldn't see,
but it fired something.
Deadly Queen!
It did shoot something at us.
It's air!
It's weaponizing masses of air!
You fetid feline!
I'll turn you into fertilizer!
I can't stamp it out!
It's like I'm pressing on
an invisible balloon!
It really does manipulate the air.
What?
Dammit it…
I can't see it, but it released
some kind of compressed air again.
Shit… Something's gonna happen!
What?
The cactus!
Sh-Shinobu!
I don't… Did Yoshikage Kira
just feel a sense of relief for…
for the cactus needles
not hitting her eyes?
What is this feeling?
Could I be worried
about someone else?
Huh, what was I thinking…
My only concern is what
might happen if this woman dies
and Jotaro Kujo discovers
I'm at this house!
That's the only reason
I'm relieved
Nothing more…
Your attack is now powerless
against me.
Your projectiles may be
invisible to the eye,
but I've deciphered
your little trick…
You simply compress air and
launch it at your opponent
in a scattering of projectiles.
Deadly Queen is no longer
defenseless against your attack.
What?!
Bastard… he injected
the mass of air into my vein!
It's traveling deeper and deeper
into my body!
I'm no doctor,
but I've heard enough to know…
Injecting more than 10ccs
of any gas into a vein
can cause blood vessel blockage
and death.
This has to be more than 10ccs!
Goddamnit!
It's no use! Blast it…
There's no other way…
I have to do it.
Deadly Queen!
I underestimated this thing.
This power to control the air…
It's more formidable than
I had imagined. What to do?
It's coming!
It's poised to attack again!
What can I do?
That was too close…
For now, I guess
I'll let it off the hook.
I'll let it live for now.
STRAY CAT
I buried the cat far away,
he told me yesterday
The cat's curse, as he said,
was just a figment of
my imagination brought on by fear.
I can't believe it…
I fainted right in front of him…
I'm so embarrassed
But…
He was late for work
and still looked after me.
It was wonderful.
It felt like, at that moment,
he really understood me.
It was the most blissful
morning of my life.
Well? Do you like it?
That Hayato…
He left without
saying goodbye again.
That little brat…
has he been watching me?
Oh, Sweetie!
That's my plate.
I know how you hate
shiitake mushrooms,
so I made sure to take them out…
Why the sudden change of heart?
You've already eaten
more than half of mine.
Don't get me wrong, I'm thrilled
you're wolfing it down.
Not so bad when you
give them a chance, huh?
Yes.
Well, I'll be going now.
Have a good day, Sweetie pie.
Hey… a goodbye kiss
would've been nice.
But we've never been closer.
Before he knows it, my seductive
love will overwhelm him.
He put his shoes on
with a shoehorn.
He was definitely wearing
25.5cm sized shoes.
Who has shoes with
two different sizes…
Plus, I've never seen
Mom and Dad get along so well.
He even scarfed down
those shiitake mushrooms
he hates so much.
This is weird, too.
Why is he practicing writing
his name over and over?
Then there's last night…
I've watched it a million times…
That's a pot with dirt.
And that has to be a bag of
cat food he's holding.
He then proceeds
to walk into his closet…
They're all wearing hats.
Is that compulsory?
Something… feels strangely off…
The attic?
W-What is that weird thing?
It's too dark… I can't make it out.
There it is. It's that bag.
Huh?
Wha—
I-It's moving!
That's not a plant…
Those are eyes!
Those are actual eyeballs
looking this way!
Could that cat food be
for this creature?
Honey.
What's the matter?
Did you forget something?
Or did you forget
my goodbye kiss?
No…
Aww…
Then what is it?
Shall I get it for you?
No, I can get it myself.
Why did he come back?
Oh no!
Huh?!
What?! Th-This thing…
Something invisible,
something almost inflated…
It's like masses of air
have my arms and neck
nailed to thin air!
He's coming up! Oh no!
The attic! I knew it! That brat…
I-It attacked me
when I tried to shut the window?
So it needs the sunlight to move?
That's it!
If they are masses of air…
Yes! So it was the sunlight.
That noise…
Did Stray Cat try to get
the cat food from the shelf
using its air-controlling abilities
and spill it on the floor?
I thought the lack of sunlight
would keep it calm…
Traces of light must be seeping in.
Still…
I suspected Hayato may have
rummaged around here,
but I suppose I can chalk it up
to overthinking.
Had that brat discovered
my true identity,
I would have had to murder him.
He has Dad's face,
but that's not Dad. Who…
Wh-Who is it… who?!
EPISODE 31
JULY 15TH (THURS), PART 1